fmrealty.com 2018-08-22

# Fonville Morisey Privacy Policy

#### Neighborhood

### Alerts

Receive alerts when a real estate change occurs near you!

Learn More...

We take great pride in our ability to recruit, train, and retain the finest quality real estate professionals.

Fonville Morisey Realty respects the privacy of every individual. Your e-mail address is obtained for internal purposes only (as they relate to marketing and the purchase and/or sale of Fonville Morisey properties) and will not be sold or shared with any unaffiliated third party other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Fonville Morisey Realty collects personal information from you (e.g. your name, postal address, e-mail address, and other data) when you provide personal data through various places on our web site. 

We may provide some of this information to our fulfillment partners for purposes of providing you with information you request, with one of our independent sales agents to follow up with you in connection with materials you request and as a part of our mailings and solicitations to prospective customers. The information you provide will also be utilized for market research purposes, for project planning or for development of prospect lists for Fonville Morisey Realty marketing. This may involve reproduction, publication, broadcast and posting of such materials and information to our affiliate companies and independent sales representatives. 

In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to communicate with you after you have sent us e-mails. If you send us e-mails, from time to time we may use information about your preferences and interests to send updates to you about Fonville Morisey Realty services, listing special offers, or information about our affiliate companies that may be of interest to you.

Fonville Morisey Realty also may disclose or exchange with others information you have provided to us if we believe that the law requires us to do so or if it is necessary to protect the rights or property of Fonville Morisey Realty, our affiliate companies, our staff or our users. 

Fonville Morisey Realty will use reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to third parties we believe to be responsible. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that may receive the information. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. For example, if we need to mail something to you, we must share your name and address with a direct mail company. We limit such third parties in their access and use of your personal information. 

Our site includes links to other Web sites. Those sites may have different privacy policies. If you click on to another Web site, you may want to check the privacy policy of that site, which will usually (but not always) be posted on the web site. Fonville Morisey Realty is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. 

Fonville Morisey Realty Website is directed to adults and is not directed to children under the age of 18. Fonville Morisey Realty complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. This Policy will be posted throughout the Fonville Morisey Realty Website. 

We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address. You may correct your personal information or select the option not to receive future Fonville Morisey Realty contacts (i.e. mailings, calls, etc.) by going emailing us at the address below. In the event you elect not to receive any future contacts from Fonville Morisey Realty, we will endeavor to remove your name from all of our contact lists; however, we can only promise to endeavor to remove you from any lists we control. We shall have no liability under this Policy for our failure to accomplish this objective. If you have questions, you should direct them to our e-Services group. 

To not receive future Fonville Morisey Realty contacts (i.e. mailings, calls, etc.) or to contact our E-Services group, contact us by clicking on the link at the bottom of the page. 

**Equal Housing Opportunity**  
We are pledged to the letter and spirit of U.S. policy for the achievement of equal housing opportunity throughout the nation. We encourage and support an affirmative advertising and marketing program in which there are no barriers to obtaining housing because of race, color, religion, sex, handicap, familial status, or national origin.

For more information, contact   
Beth McNally  
919-785-4363  
DQuackenbush@FMRealty.com
